Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-132
  - Koll, 2/1989-11/1989; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Koppell, 7/1991-12/1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Landau, 3/1986-9/88; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Malott, 7/1987-10/88; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - McClotchy, 2/88-8/1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - McGee, 9/1987-8/1989; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Moldaw, 3/1987-8/1990; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Shorenstein, 2/88-8/1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Swig, 8/88-8/1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Wheatley, 10/1985-9/1989; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - White, 11/1984-1/1985; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Willard, 5/1987-8/88; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Gifts and Gifts Processing, Miscellaneous, 2/1991-5/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-1 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-1)
  - General Motors Corporation, 10/1982-2/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-25 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-25)
  - Glenmede Trust Company, 8/1991-8/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-26 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-26)
  - Hewlett Packard Company, 6/1984-8/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-28 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-28)
  - William Lane, 6/80-8/1990; AD 12.10.3/5-31 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-31)
  - Packard, David and Lucile, Gift, 9/1984-8/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-38 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-38)
  - Sol Price, 10/1985-11/1989; AD 12.10.3/5-39 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-39)
  - Sterling, Dr. J.E. Wallace, 11/1982-8/1989; AD 12.10.3/5-43 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-43)
  - Lane Publishing Company, 9/1984-2/1991; AD 12.10.3/5-45 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-45)
  - Syntex Corporation, 4/1982-8/1992; AD 12.10.3/5-46 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-46)
  - Foundations and Corporations, Miscellaneous, 2/1990-8/1992; AD 12.10.4 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, Inc., 9/1982-1/1991; AD 12.10.4/12 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/12)
  - Boswell Foun dation, 7/1983-10/88; AD 12.10.4/21 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/21)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 4/1982-8/1992; AD 12.10.4/37 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/37)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 12/1987-9/1990; AD 12.10.4/47 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/47)
  - Cowell Foundation, SH, 12/1982-6/1992; AD 12.104/50 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.104/50)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc., 9/1982-10/1986; AD 12.10.4/51 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/51)
  - Danforth Foundation, 12/1982-9/1989; AD 12.10.4/55 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/55)
  - C and H Dreyfus, 12/1982-4/88; AD 12.10.4/60 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/60)
  - Educational Foundation, 10/1982-7/1991; AD 12.10.4/62 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/62)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 4/1983-5/1992; AD 12.10.4/67 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/67)
  - Getty Trust Fund, 7/1984-1/1991; AD 12.10.4/80 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/80)
  - Johnson Foundation, 12/1982-11/1990; AD 12.10.4/107 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/107)
  - Kresge Foundation, 8/1982-2/1992; AD 12.10.4/117 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/117)
  - Leakey Foundation, 9/1984-7/1987; AD 12.10.4/118 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/118)
  - Markey, Lucille P., 9/1984-8/1992; AD 12.10.4/131 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/131)
  - Systems Development, 8/1982-9/1984; AD 12.10.4/240 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/240)
  - Tinker Foundation, Inc. The, 6/1983-12/1990; AD 12.10.4/246 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/246)
  - Fairchild Foundation, 12/1982-12/1990; AD 12.10.4/271 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/271)
  - Tanner, Obert, C and Grace A., 9/1981-6/1991; AD 12.10.4/280 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/280)
  - Gianini Foundation-BofA, 10/1982-2/1992; AD 12.10.4/292 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/292)
  - Christensen Fund, 12/1982-2/1990; AD 12.10.4/295 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.4/295)
  - Combined Health Agencies Drive (CHAD), United Way, 6/1991-8/1992; AD 12.10.8 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.8)
  - Technology Licensing/Patent/Copyrights, 5/88-12/1991; AD 12.11 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.11)
  - Oregon Expressway, 10/88-8/1989; AD.12.12.3 (Box 8, Folder AD.12.12.3)
  - Real Estate Programs, 2/88-6/1992; AD 12.13 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.13)
  - Land and Buildings, 1/1991-8/1992; AD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Use of Land and Facilities, 2/88-7/1992; AD 12.14.1 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.1)
  - Earthquake, 1989, 1/1990-5/1992; AD 12.14.1/2 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.1/2)
  - Near West Campus Project, 9/1987-11/1991; AD 12.14.7/31 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/31)
  - Memorial Church, 1/1989-7/1992; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/50)
  - Miscellaneous and Ad Hoc Organization, 9/1991-8/1992; 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Super Bowl, 5/1982-2/1987; 1.2 (Box 9, Folder 1.2)
  - World Affairs Council, 9/1985-2/1992; 1.31 (Box 9, Folder 1.31)
  - Consortium on financing Higher Education (COFHE), 11/1990-7/1992; 3.1 (Box 9, Folder 3.1)
  - California Academy of Science, 9/1991-6/1992; 3.2 (Box 9, Folder 3.2)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, 4/1991-1/1992; 3.22 (Box 9, Folder 3.22)
  - Am Assoc of University Professors (AAUP), 10/1982-6/1992; 3.6 (Box 9, Folder 3.6)
  - Am Academy of Arts and Sciences, 5/1991-8/1992; 3.7 (Box 9, Folder 3.7)
  - Am Council on Education (ACE), 10/1991-8/1992; 3.8 (Box 9, Folder 3.8)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and, 11/1991-8/1992; 3.1 (Box 9, Folder 3.1)
  - World Peace Groups (Beyond War, Bike-A-Thon), 10/1984-11/1989; 6.1 (Box 9, Folder 6.1)
  - CA State Universities, 12/1982-9/1989; 8.17 (Box 9, Folder 8.17)
  - Cornell University, 11/1979-10/1991; 8.19 (Box 9, Folder 8.19)
  - Princeton University, 6/1984-7/1992; 8.36 (Box 9, Folder 8.36)
  - Eight Universities, 2/1990-7/1992; 8.39 (Box 9, Folder 8.39)
  - University of CA (all campuses), 1/1991-10/1991; 8.43 (Box 9, Folder 8.43)
  - University of Southern CA (USC), 9/1984-12/1990; 8.49 (Box 9, Folder 8.49)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC), 5/1991-3/1992; 8.52 (Box 9, Folder 8.52)
  - Yale, 11/80-5/1991; 8.53 (Box 9, Folder 8.53)
  - Western College Association (WCA), 1/1983-3/1990; 8.54 (Box 9, Folder 8.54)
  - Inaugurations-other schools, 1/1990-3/1992; 8.55 (Box 9, Folder 8.55)
  - Research, Miscellaneous, 10/1987-6/1992; RO (Box 9, Folder RO)
  - Sponsored Projects, 12/1990-5/1991; R1 (Box 9, Folder R1)
  - Vice Provost-Research, 7/1989-8/1992; R1.1 (Box 9, Folder R1.1)
  - Institute for International Studies, 2/1992-7/1992; R1.12 (Box 9, Folder R1.12)
  - AIDS (Acquired Immune Deficiency), 3/1986-2/1990; R1.13 (Box 9, Folder R1.13)
  - Research Proposals, Misc., 6/80-10/1990; R4 (Box 9, Folder R4)
  - Academic Council, 11/80-7/1992; C1.1 (Box 9, Folder C1.1)
  - Senate of the Academic Council Correspondence, 1/1991-5/1992; C2.1 (Box 9, Folder C2.1)
  - Academic Council Senate Report #1, 5/1990-12/1991; C2.4 (Box 9, Folder C2.4)
  - Advisory Board, 1/1991-8/1992; C3 (Box 9, Folder C3)
  - Committee on Acad Appraisal and Achievement (CAAA), 6/1984-8/1992; C5.1 (Box 9, Folder C5.1)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs (C-FSP), 2/1984-3/1987; C5.2 (Box 9, Folder C5.2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US), 1/1986-2/1991; C5.7 (Box 9, Folder C5.7)
  - University Committees, 11/1984-9/1990; C6 (Box 9, Folder C6)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 10/1982-8/93; C6.1 (Box 9, Folder C6.1)
  - Committee on Affirmative Action in Staff Employment, 5/1979-7/1992; C6.10 (Box 9, Folder C6.10)
  - Committee on Faculty Recruitment and Retention, 1/1991-3/91;4/1991-10/1991; C6.5.2 (Box 9, Folder C6.5.2)
  - Commitee on Land and Building Development (UCLBD), 6/1987-5/1992; C6.6 (Box 10, Folder C6.6)
  - Subcommittee on Faculty, 10/1983-8/1986; C6.6.1 (Box 10, Folder C6.6.1)
  - University Panel on Outdoor Art, 5/1983-6/86;9/1986-3/1992; C6.6.2 (Box 10, Folder C6.6.2)
  - Committee on Earthquake Preparedness (CEP), 10/1982-12/1991; C6.7 (Box 10, Folder C6.7)
  - Committee on Services to Students (C-OSS), 9/72-9/1985; C6.9 (Box 10, Folder C6.9)
  - University Committee on Minority Issues (UCMI), 12/1989-8/1991; C6.9.2 (Box 10, Folder C6.9.2)
  - Commission on International Studies, 10/1979-11/1985; C7.6 (Box 10, Folder C7.6)
  - Admin Panel on Health and Safety, 9/1982-8/1992; C8.10 (Box 10, Folder C8.10)
  - Admin Panel on Lab Animal Care, 10/1982-3/1992; C 8.11 (Box 10, Folder C 8.11)
  - Admin Panel on Internal Affirmative Action, 4/1983-12/1990; C8.12 (Box 10, Folder C8.12)
  - Admin Panel on External Aftirmative Action, 7/1986-8/1992; C8.13 (Box 10, Folder C8.13)
  - Admin Panel on University Press (PUP), 4/73-7/88; C8.6 (Box 10, Folder C8.6)
  - Legislative and Judicial Bodies for Student Conduct, 6/1985-4/1992; C9 (Box 10, Folder C9)
  - Student Conduct Legislative Council (SCLC), 3/1981-5/85;8/8/80-7/1990; C9.3 (Box 10, Folder C9.3)
  - Honor Code Commission, 8/80-10/88; C9.5 (Box 10, Folder C9.5)
  - Admin. Panel on Privacy of Information, 10/72-1/1984; C11 (Box 10, Folder C11)
  - Alumni Relations, 4/1991-8/1992; AL1 (Box 10, Folder AL1)
  - Alumni Conference, 9/1982-2/1992; AL 1.7 (Box 10, Folder AL 1.7)
  - Stanford Magazine, The, 1/80-11/1991; AL 1.12 (Box 10, Folder AL 1.12)
  - Stanford Associates, 10/80-7/1992; AL 2 (Box 10, Folder AL 2)
  - Alumni Clubs, Miscellaneous, 6/1983-5/1992; AL 3.4 (Box 10, Folder AL 3.4)
  - Other Alumni Groups, 11/80-11/1984; AL 4 (Box 10, Folder AL 4)
  - Graduate Studies, 5/1990-8/1992; AA 1.13 (Box 10, Folder AA 1.13)
  - Graduate Studies, 10/1987-11/1991; AA 1.13.2 (Box 10, Folder AA 1.13.2)
  - Dean of Graduate Studies, 3/1989-11/1990; AA 1.13.4 (Box 10, Folder AA 1.13.4)
  - Dean's Retreat, 8/88-11/1990; AA 1.5.2 (Box 10, Folder AA 1.5.2)
  - Faculty and Acad Appointment, 6/1982-6/1984; AA 2.3.2 (Box 10, Folder AA 2.3.2)
  - Tenure Policy, 10/1982-5/1992; AA 2.6.9 (Box 10, Folder AA 2.6.9)
  - Fellows of the University, 9/1985-6/92;10/1982-8/1985; AA 2.9 (Box 10, Folder AA 2.9)
  - Teaching and Research Assistants /Associates, 7/1985-7/1992; AA 2.11 (Box 11, Folder AA 2.11)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1/88-8/1991; AA 3 (Box 11, Folder AA 3)
  - Undergraduate Advising Center, 11/1990-6/1991; AA 3.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.1)
  - Degrees /Honorary Degrees, 6/1979-2/1992; AA 3.10 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.10)
  - Educational Innovations, 11/1983-8/1992; AA 3.11 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.11)
  - Stanford National Rating, 5/1983-9/1991; AA 3.4 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.4)
  - Western Culture Requirement, 4/1990-8/1992; AA 3.5.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.5.1)
  - Continuing Education, 2/1990-5/1992; AA 3.6 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.6)
  - Freshman Advising, 12/1982-5/1990; AA 3.7 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.7)
  - Curriculum, 10/1984-5/1990; AA 3.9 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.9)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 8/1987-8/1992; AA 4.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1)
  - Values, Technology Sciences and Society (VTSS), 5/1985-7/1992; AA 4.1.1/1 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.1/1)
  - Humanities Center, 1/1991-8/1992; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.1/2)
  - King Papers (Martin Luther, Jr.), 1/1989-11/1990; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.1/3)
  - Jewish Studies Program, 10/1985-4/1992; AA 4.1.1/5 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.1/5)
  - African and Afro-American Studies Program, 5/1983-7/1992; AA 4.1.4 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.4)
  - Anthropology, Department of, 1/1989-3/1992; AA 4.1.5 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.5)
  - Archaeology, Department of, 5/1985-10/1990; AA 4.1.6 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.6)
  - Applied Physics, Dept. of, 10/1982-5/1992; AA 4.1.8 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.8)
  - Rodin Collection, Cantor Gift, 9/80-3/1991; AA 4.1.9/1 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.9/1)
  - Asian Languages, Dept. of, 1/1981-10/1992; AA 4.1.10 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.10)
  - Biological Sciences, Dept. of, 6/1990-7/1992; AA 4.1.12 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.12)
  - Center for Conservation Biology, 11/1986-9/1991; AA 4.1.12/1 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.12/1)
  - Communication, Dept. of, 3/1991-6/1992; AA 4.1.15 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.15)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 2/1987-7/1992; AA 4.1.17 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.17)
  - Drama, Dept. of, 10/1982-6/1992; AA 4.1.18 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.18)
  - Economics, Dept. of, 1/1989-5/1992; AA 4.1.20 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.1.20)
  - Center for Economic Policy Research (CEPR), 1/88-5/1992; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.20/1)
  - English, Dept. of, 2/1989-2/1992; AA 4.1.21 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.21)
  - French and Italian, Dept. of, 5/1983-5/1992; AA 4.1.22 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.22)
  - German, Dept. of, 6/1983-8/1992; AA 4.1.24 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.24)
  - History, Dept. of, 5/1983-5/1992; AA 4.1.25 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.25)
  - Human Biology, Program in, 9/1989-8/1992; AA 4.1.26 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.26)
  - Mathematics, Dept. of, 8/1982-5/1992; AA 4.1.27 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.27)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), 5/1989-7/1992; AA 4.1.28 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.28)
  - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreations, Dept. (DAPER), 4/1990-11/90;6/1982-8/1992; AA 4.1.30 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Astronomy, 5/1985-7/1985; AA 4.1.33/1 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.33/1)
  - African and Afro-American Studies Program, 5/1983-7/1992; AA 4.1.40 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.40)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1/1983-10/1985; AA 4.1.42 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.42)
  - Religious Studies, Dept. of, 3/1983-6/1987; AA 4.1.47 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.47)
  - Center for Research in Intl. Studies (CRIS), 7/1983-7/1990; AA 4.10 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.10)
  - Graduate School of Business (GSB), 1/1991-8/1992; AA 4.2 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.2)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1/1991-6/1992; AA 4.3 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.3)
  - Geology, Dept. of, AA 4.3.1 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.3.1)
  - School of Engineering, 9/1991-8/1992; AA 4.4 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.4)
  - Engineering-Economic Systems, Dept. of, 8/1985-4/1991; AA 4.4.4 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.4.4)
  - Industrial Engineering and Engineering Management, 3/1985-12/1991; AA 4.4.6 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 1/1991-8/1992; AA 4.6 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Hoover Institution, 4/1987-8/1992; AA 4.9 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Libraries, Stanford, AA 4.12 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.12)
  - (SLAC) Stanford Linear Accelerator, 1/1990-5/1992; AA 4.13 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.13)
  - School of Law, 1/1989-8/1992; AA 4.15 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.15)
  - East Palo Alto Community Law Project, 2/1984-9/1986; AA 4.15./1 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.15./1)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 11/1989-12/1991; AA 4.17 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SUH Board of Directors, 10/1991-8/1992; AA 4.17.2 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - New Children's Hospital, 2/1990-7/1992; AA 4.17.5/1 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.5/1)
  - Animal Rights Issues, 8/1990-8/1992; AA 4.17.6 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.6)
  - Awards and Prizes, Misc., 11/1991-8/1992; AA 5 (Box 13, Folder AA 5)
  - Grants, Misc., 10/1983-11/1991; AA 6 (Box 13, Folder AA 6)
  - Endowed Chairs, Prof. Misc., 7/1983-2/1992; AA 10 (Box 13, Folder AA 10)
  - Proposed Professorships, 7/1983-2/1992; AA 10.1 (Box 13, Folder AA 10.1)
  - President's Office Chrons, 7/1991-12/1992 (Box 14)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1995-039
  - Chrons, 1991-01 (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991-02 (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991-03 (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991-04 (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991-05 (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991-06 (Box 1)
  - Other Universities, 1/25/1991-12/5/1992; 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AAU, 11/90-12/90; 1991-92; 8.7 (Box 1, Folder 8.7)
  - David Starr Jordan-A Register of His Papers in the Hoover Institution Archives (Box 1)
  - Library of the Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace Stanford Humanities Review, Winter 1993 (Box 1)
  - Outside organizations, Jan-March 1991; 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 9/89-1991; 3.43 (Box 2, Folder 3.43)
  - NCAA, 1990-1991; 3.44 (Box 2, Folder 3.44)
  - Pac-10 Conference, 1991; 3.47 (Box 2, Folder 3.47)
  - Pac-10 Conference, 1992; 3.47 (Box 2, Folder 3.47)
  - Stanford University Annual Financial Report for year (Box 2)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 6/1991-12/1991; C2 (Box 3, Folder C2)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 1/1992-6/1992; C2 (Box 3, Folder C2)
  - Intitute of International Studies, 9/1992-12/1992; R1.1.12 (Box 3, Folder R1.1.12)
  - Intitute of International Studies, 1/1991-1/1992; R1.1.12 (Box 3, Folder R1.1.12)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1998-129
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Materials transferred from Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers (SC0672).
  - 1983 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1984 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1985 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1986 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1987 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1988 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1989 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1990 Centennial Year Opening Convocation 9/30/90 - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
  - 1991 Commencement Red Book - Donald Kennedy (Box 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2006-044
  - Presidential Portrait (negative), by Brigitte Carnochan, 1995 Sep (Box 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-139
  - Donald Kennedy Personal – Sabbatical, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Presidency, Scientific Fraud / Stanford & Rebholz, Manly (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Post-presidency: Human Biology (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hum. Bio. Environmental Science (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Post-presidency: IIS/Provost’s Committee on Environmental Science (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, Post-presidency general (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Post-presidency: Human Biology Program (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Post-presidency: Development (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letters of support regarding the Indirect Cost Recovery issue [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letters of support regarding the Indirect Cost Recovery issue [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letters of support regarding Donald Kennedy’s resignation [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letters of support regarding Donald Kennedy’s resignation [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letters of Support regarding resignation [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letters of Support regarding resignation [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UCLA Extension Lecture Series, Los Angeles, CA, 1979 Oct 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 20/20 – Kennedy [CONFIDENTIAL] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Donald Kennedy Personal – US Government Documents (Sec. Clear., IRS, etc.) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letters of support regarding Donald Kennedy’s resignation (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Letters of support regarding resignation (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Employment – IDC Vindication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Letters of support regarding resignation (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Overhead Charges, Letters of support (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Donald Kennedy personal- newspaper articles, etc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Norman Maclean invitation acceptance & Introduction by Wallace Stegner, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-188
  - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Affairs [CURA] 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CURA meeting plans 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CURA filing (assorted clippings, reports, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CURA filing 2 (assorted clippings, reports, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CURA filing 3 (assorted clippings, reports, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CURA filing 4 (assorted clippings, reports, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Deans’ Council Meeting 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Deans’ Council members 1987-89 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Deans’ Council calendar (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Deans’ Council agenda plans (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Deans’ Council back-up file (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Deans’ Council notes (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Deans’ Council index master (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Deans’ Council minutes 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Deans’ Council miscellaneous 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Human Resources Council book (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Human Resources Council calendars (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Human Resources Council members (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Human Resources Council background (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Human Resources Council official file (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Human Resources Council agenda (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Human Resources Council minutes and notes, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Human Resources Council minutes 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Human Resources philosophy 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Stanford University Cabinet 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Provosts Advisory Committee on Development (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Binder: DPC Meeting Book (agenda, calendars, minutes, etc.) 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Binder: Unlabelled; contains Provost’s Advisory Committee on Development memos, policies, etc. 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Folder: miscellaneous materials (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Binder: DPDB / FRAPS (Fundraising Approval and Priority Requests) 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Binder: DPC / PACD Chron September 1991-July 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Binder: DPC (Development Priorities Committee) / GFG (Provost’s Advisory Committee on Development) Chron January 1991-September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council Naming Policy 1984-91 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council memoranda and email (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council (binder): executive session minutes 1987-89 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council (binder): unofficial records executive session 1980-86 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council (binder): minutes 1985-89 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council (binder): naming procedures and policies 1985-89 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council (binder): naming procedures and policies 1983-87 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Binder: Stanford Operations Council 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Binder: Stanford University Cabinet agenda and minutes 1990-92 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Binder: Stanford University Cabinet, JHM Chron [agenda and minutes] 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Binder: Stanford University Cabinet minutes 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University Cabinet agenda, minutes, and other materials 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Cabinet miscellaneous 1990-92 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Research requests (Stanford University Cabinet) 1988-91 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - UC correspondence 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Minutes for IRS audit (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Campus review plan May 19, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Calendar 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - University Cabinet / Council meetings 1990-92 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miscellany (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Council Manual (1 of 2) 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council Manual (2 of 2) 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council masters (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council miscellaneous 1986-90 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council old lists (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council worksheets (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council draft minutes (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council meeting book 1988-90 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Agenda minutes (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council Sept. 19, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Council Sept. 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Council Aug. 15, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Council July 11, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Council May 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Council April 1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council March 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Council February 1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Council January 31, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Council January 17, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Council Dec. 20, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Council Nov. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Council Oct. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Council Oct. 4, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Council Sept. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Council August 1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)